<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuideKolkata</string>
    <string name="Heading_Eden_Gardens">Eden Gardens</string>
    <string name="Heading_Dakshineswar_Kali_Temple">Dakshineswar Kali Temple</string>
    <string name="Heading_Victoria_Memorial_Hall">Victoria Memorial Hall</string>
    <string name="Heading_Mother_House">Mother House</string>
    <string name="Heading_Howrah_Bridge">Howrah Bridge</string>
    <string name="Heading_Park_Street">Park Street</string>
    <string name="Heading_South_Park_Street_Cemetery">South Park Street Cemetery</string>
    <string name="Heading_Eco_Tourism_Park">Eco Tourism Park</string>
    <string name="Heading_Science_City">Science City</string>
    <string name="Heading_Birla_Temple">Birla Temple</string>
    <string name="Heading_Barbeque_Nation">Barbeque Nation</string>
    <string name="Heading_Baan_Thai">Baan Thai</string>
    <string name="Heading_Ballygunge_Place_6">6 Ballygunge Place</string>
    <string name="Heading_Bar_B_Q">Bar B Q</string>
    <string name="Heading_Oh_Calcutta">Oh Calcutta</string>
    <string name="Heading_Arsalan">Arsalan</string>
    <string name="Heading_Peter_Cat">Peter Cat</string>
    <string name="Heading_Mocambo">Mocambo</string>
    <string name="Heading_Dum_Pukht">Dum Pukht</string>
    <string name="Heading_Aaheli">Aaheli</string>
    <string name="Heading_Hyatt_Regency_Kolkata">Hyatt Regency Kolkata</string>
    <string name="Heading_The_Oberoi_Grand">The Oberoi Grand</string>
    <string name="Heading_Taj_Bengal_Kolkata">Taj Bengal Kolkata</string>
    <string name="Heading_ITC_Sonar">ITC Sonar</string>
    <string name="Heading_The_Gateway_Hotel_EM_Bypass">The Gateway Hotel EM Bypass</string>
    <string name="Heading_Novotel_Kolkata_Hotel_and_Residences">Novotel Kolkata Hotel and Residences</string>
    <string name="Heading_Senses_Hotel">Senses Hotel</string>
    <string name="Heading_Tatvam_Residency">Tatvam Residency</string>
    <string name="Heading_Monotel_Luxury_Business_Hotel">Monotel Luxury Business Hotel</string>
    <string name="Description_Eden_Gardens"> Eden Gardens is the one of the most popular cricket grounds in world.
                  It is really amazing to be there during any driver match or and festival.
                  Its really enjoyable place.."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Dakshineswar_Kali_Temple">"It is extremely popular among the locals and has a good crowd.
        Pretty much away from the city. Its a big temple and lots of foreigners are also seen here."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Victoria_Memorial_Hall">
         "Victoria Memorial or Victoria Memorial Hall was built to commemorate the peak of the British Empire in India"
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Mother_House">
       "The Missionaries of Charity's Mother House is a holy place of pilgrimage and reverence for
        those who are searching for a more meaningful existence."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Howrah_Bridge">
        "Howrah Bridge also known as Rabindra Setu is a suspension type balanced cantilever bridge
        located in West Bengal, India. It connects Howrah and Kolkata."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Park_Street">
        "Park Street is a famous thoroughfare in the city of Kolkata (formerly Calcutta), India.
        The street runs through what was a deer park of Sir Elijah Impey"
    </string>
    <string name="Description_South_Park_Street_Cemetery">
       South Park Street Cemetery is located on Mother Teresa Sarani, Kolkata, India.
        The road used to be called Park Street, and prior to that Burial Ground Road.
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Eco_Tourism_Park">
        "Eco Tourism Park surrounds a picturesque water body that measures 104 acres in surface area.
         It has an island in the middle, which can be reached by a bridge"
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Science_City">
        "Science City, Kolkata is the largest science centre in the Indian subcontinent under
         National Council of Science Museums (NCSM)"
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Birla_Temple">
        "Birla Temple Kolkata is a popular sightseeing spot of the city.
         The temple is dedicated to the consortium of Lord Krishna and his beloved Radha."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Barbeque_Nation">
        "Barbecue nation and its sea food is extremely delicious. Its very crowded most often.
         Good dining on budget. Large variants of sea food are served here."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Baan_Thai">
        "This hotel has Great Ambience.. Amazing hospitality by the staff.
         Best thai restaurant in Kolkata.. Overall great experience."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Ballygunge_Place_6">
        "Excellent food, great spread for vegetarians too, impressive hospitality.
         Must visit if you are interested in sampling local cuisine."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Bar_B_Q">
        "Great place for Unlimited Kebabs, Wholesome food....
        famous for its unlimited kebab buffet platter"
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Oh_Calcutta">
        "From Smoked Hilsa to Dub Sandesh, every single dish is just awesome
        , Chitagong Masala murgi , Borisaler Chingri Polao.. every dish was just mouthwatering."

    </string>
    <string name="Description_Arsalan">
        "It's been long time they are serving delicious biryani..if u been to Kolkata
         you should just arsanal for yummy biryani and firni as there speciality"
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Peter_Cat">
        "This is the best place to taste kebabs. They offers very good kebabs.
         Prices are reasonable. Week days are less crowded as compared to weekends."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Mocambo">
        "The food here is exotic and the ambience superb. The service is also remarkable.
         This restaurant is an ideal place to go with family and friends."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Dum_Pukht">
        "This is a real royal treat for your senses. Be treated like the ancient Indian royals.
         Food is good and service is even better."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Aaheli">
        "A complete and well laid out Bengali fine dining experience.
        Though prices on a bit higher side but the service and ambiance is very nice."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Hyatt_Regency_Kolkata">
        "Excellent stay and dinning, very near to Dum Dum Airport.
        Besides EM bypass. Well connected with the City. Attached to Salt Lake City of Kolkata"
    </string>
    <string name="Description_The_Oberoi_Grand">
        "Nice hotel with amazing hospitality by the staff. Thai food was very tasty
        ....Swimming pool timings can be extended upto 10 pm instead of 7 pm"
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Taj_Bengal_Kolkata">
        "Excellent place to stay both for business and pleasure The reception is manned by
         extremely polite receptionists who go the extra mile to make the stay comfortable"
    </string>
    <string name="Description_ITC_Sonar">
        "This is by far the best hotel Kolkata has to offer whether it be a business or a personal trip.
        Staff here is the best example of the philosophy of Indian hospitality"
    </string>
    <string name="Description_The_Gateway_Hotel_EM_Bypass">
        "Cleanness is the best part of this hotel. food is very delicious
        and service staff is very attentive."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Novotel_Kolkata_Hotel_and_Residences">
        "Novotel Kolkata is a fantastic hotel to stay. Amidst the newer area of Kolkata,
         it is huge with very good rooms and ambience."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Senses_Hotel">
        "This hotel is placed in nice location, particularly very suitable for people visiting IT
        offices in Kolkata. Comfortable stay, courteous and friendly staff.
        Well maintained rooms and excellent service"
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Tatvam_Residency">
        "Home away from home. The rooms are quite spacious. Staff very helpful.
        Tasty food. Overall ambience very good. All in all a very good hotel."
    </string>
    <string name="Description_Monotel_Luxury_Business_Hotel">
        "Located in the business centre of salt lake, kolkata and value for money luxury business hotel.
        Very good option or overnighter or long stay for business purpose. "
    </string>
     <string name="Season">
        "Kolkata. The city enjoys winter from November to February. The low temperature during
         this season ranges between 9 and 11 degrees Celsius. It is the best time to visit
         Kolkata as the weather is cool and pleasant too. "
    </string>
    <string name="tab1">Places</string>
    <string name="tab2">Accomodation</string>
    <string name="tab3">Dinning</string>
    <string name="tab4">Season</string>
    <string name="title_activity_places">PlacesActivity</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
